Yamada Tetsuo

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

3-30, Kita 43-jo Higashi 15, Higashi-ku Sapporo, Alaska

wendyhotdog101@gmail.com

8131-925-7297

My expertise ranges from different programming languages to responsive frameworks to a vast array of knowledge in other areas My focus is on clean, elegant, and efficient codes and I am able to work on new and existing micro-sites, landing pages, templates, and provide guidance and troubleshooting support to clients.

I have solid experience in React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB and Next.js.

Among my experience are blockchain smart contracts, NFT marketplace, and Olympus DAO fork. I am passionate about front-end development as technology innovation, and I have the drive and energy needed to consistently exceed expectations.

I look forward to being a part of a growing company as a front-end developer where I can utilize exceptional programming and interpersonal skills acquired to contribute to your company's success.

Technologies:

Git, GitHub, HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, Typescript, Python, Django, React, Angular, Vue, React Native, Ionic, Flutter, Node, Express, Nest, Ruby, Django, Agile, AWS, Docker, Jest, Mocha, Solidity, Web3.js.

It is my goal to understand the clients' needs clearly and to deliver a high-quality project on time at an optimal cost.

Professional Experience

Senior Front end Designer | *Tsukiden Global Solutions Inc* | *November* 2018 - October 2019

- Led the front-end development of a smart price recommendations platform used by large retail and e-Commerce clients.
- Worked with developers around the world to build software applications.
- Implemented and managed companies Design System library.
- Profiled critical components, eliminating wasting renders which dramatically improved performance.
- Simplified the project structure, emphasizing re-usability and scalability.

Technologies: React, Typescript

Full Stack Developer | UBITUS INC. | February 2020 - November 2022

- Completed 3 contracts with UBITUS INC.
- Developed single web page applications and taught other developers to build such applications.
- Built from scratch admin platform for managing platform's database entities and users using React, Node and Mongoose.
- Implemented complex UI components with React/Typescript and SCSS.
- Improved the UX by creating several DnD-Based components.

Technologies: MongoDB, Node.js, React, JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, Bootstrap

Education

Master of Software Engineering | The University of Tokyo at Tokyo | April 2012 - March 2016

- Followed my passion in a core of prototyping and cloud computing classes.
- Excelled in user experience and user interfaces.
- Pursued a Generalist Scholars grant to study software architecture.

Bachelor of Science | Kyoto University at Kyoto | April 2016 - March 2018

- Majoring in Computer Science and Technology.
- Bachelor of Science

Key Skills

- CSS / HTML
- React / Redux / React Native / Next.js
- MongoDB / SQL
- Python / Django
- ExpressJS / Node.js
- PHP / Laravel
- JavaScript && TypeScript
- Vue.js / Nuxt.js / Angular.js
- Web 3.js / Ether.js